# Yuji Oshiro

Lake Forest, CA // (949) 309-6900 // <a href="mailto:iamyujioshiro@gmail.com">iamyujioshiro@gmail.com</a>

## Summary

Computer Science student working towards transferring to a 4-year University for the Fall 2022 semester while obtaining an associate degree in Computer Science. I have taken part in several hackathons building web/desktop applications and am currently building an Android application with a team of 4 for a month-long app building competition.

### Education

Irvine Valley College, Associate Degree, Computer Science, 2022 (I am currently applying to transfer to a 4-year university within California. Expected to obtain a bachelor's degree in 2024.)

I have taken C/C++, Intro to Python, and calculus courses. I have also completed the Foundations course for an open-source web development curriculum called The Odin Project and am going through the Full Stack JavaScript course in my free time.

## Experience

#### CodePath.org [iOS Tech Fellow]

October 2021 – Present

- Tech lead for CodePath.org iOS course
- Teach programming fundamentals to students using iOS and Swift
- Code review and debug student's code
- Facilitate and manage team building within the class and community building on campus

#### Taco Bell [Level 1 Service Desk Analyst]

February 2021 – July 2021

- Provide technical assistance to stores with software and hardware issues
- Identify issues and provide accurate troubleshooting to resolve problems
- Act as first line analysis within the service desk chain to resolve issues quickly and accurately or escalate with proper notes as needed
- Manage and prioritize work activities with minimal supervision to ensure field operations continue without interruption

#### The Darkroom [Assistant Production Manager]

May 2018 - March 2020

- Oversee a team of lab technicians in the processing of film
- Ensure quality of work remains consistent from order to order
- Take note of any issues with machines related to production and repair when necessary, or report it to the responsible party

#### Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, C/C++, Java, Python, Swift
- Software: Atom, Git/GitHub, Xcode, Android Studio
- Hardware: Comfortable working with PCs, Macs, and mobile devices